Yuri.
うえはら (上原)百合
Yuri?
なお (菜緒)百合って…
So she's Uehara's girlfriend.
(菜緒) この人が上原君の?
Ouch!
上原)イッテ! ツテ
What're you whining about? Pulling a disappearing act like that!
(百合)イツテーじゃないわよ 突然いなくなって
Do you realize how worried we were about you?
こっちが どんだけ心配したと思ってんの こと忠つ
Ow!
(上原)イテテテテ 丁丁丁丁 (百合)何生意気に
You lost weight again, didn't you?
(百合)痩せたんじゃない? 一段と
No I didn't.
(上原)んなことねーし
-You look like a zombie. -It's just the lighting.
(百合)顔色ゾンビみたい (上原)明かりのせいだろ
I bet you're just eating junk, aren't you?
(百合)どうせろくなもん 食べてなかったんでしょ
It's way better than your cooking.
お前の料理より はるかにマシ
Hey, I'm still sick!
俺は病人だぞ! (百合)だから!
We'll have a proper talk together about your future and--
これからのことはお互い もう1回ちゃんと話し合って
No way.
無理
What?
は?
You know, I don't think you even have the right to talk like that.
っていうかお前に そんなこと言う権利あんのかよ?
Whose fault do you think it was that I left?
誰のせいで 俺が出てったと思ってんだよ
Hmm? Let me think.
佰合)え~?誰だっけ?
-Hey! -I'm just kidding.
おい!)冗談よ冗談 (百合)冗談よ冗談 冗詼
In any case, if you're going to wreck your health
何にしてもこれ以上 一人暮らしを続けて体壊すようなら
because you're living alone, then I'm dragging you back home.
何が何でも連れて帰るから
You don't even know where I live.
俺の家知らねーくせに
The doctor told me.
先生に聞きました
I couldn't help it. They asked me.
だって聞かれたから
You blabber.
余計なこと
How dare you scold the person you owe your life to?
(百合)命の恩人に 絡むんじゃないわよ
Would you cut it out with the hitting?
お前どんだけ 暴力振るうんだよ
You ungrateful smart-ass!
佰刽 この恩知らずが偉そうに
I am not ungrateful.
偉そうになんかしてねーよ
Then at least try to act it.
佰刽もっと しおらしくしろっつーの
Why you!
仩原)は?
OK, I'll be going now.
(菜緒) じゃあ私はここで
OK.
(上原)おお
Hey, at least thank her.
あんたお礼の1つぐらい 言いなさいよ
Thanks... for all your help.
いろいろ助かった つに
It's OK. Take care of yourself.
うん お大事に
Yeah.
おお
Ah! Wait a second. Let's go together.
めつちょっと待って 一緒に出よ
I want to ask you about Hisashi.
ひさし 久志のことで 聞きたいこともあるし
I want to go to tell the doctor thanks.
佰刽ちょっと 先生に挨拶してくるね
Wait for me in the lobby, OK?
ロビーで待っててくれる?
OK.
(菜緒)はい
That was a wedding ring, right?
あれって結婚指輪だよね
Wait! That means...
え?ってことは
they're having an affair?
不倫!? 个1冊
An affair...
Rfii...
Uehara and that pretty woman...
上原君と あのきれいな女の人が…
We can't. I have a husband--
ダメよ 私には主人が
Yuri. I want you to be mine.
百合 俺のものになってよ
Hisashi.
久志…
No, no, no!
(菜緒)イヤッ…おお~
That... that's for grownups! For adults!
おおおお 大人だ大人の世界
But... Uehara seemed so right in that scene.
でも上原君 ちょっと似合っちゃってるかも
What's wrong? Are you feeling sick?
どうした? 具合でも悪くなった?
Oh... no. I'm fine.
あ…いえ大丈夫です
I'm Uehara Yuri.
私上原百合って言います
Here's my card. My number's on it.
これ一応名刺 連絡先書いてあるから
Uehara
JEA...
Oh, I'm Hisashi's sister-in-law.
佰刽ああ私 久志の義理の姉になるのよね
His older brother is Takuya. He's my husband.
久志の兄貴卓也っていうんだけど 彼が私の旦那
Now I see.
なるほど
What?
えっ!? 上原君と兄嫁がふり ...
Huh?
ん?
I'm Yoshikawa Nao.
よしかわ 私吉川です 吉川菜緒
Nao. That's a pretty name.
菜緒ちゃんか かわいい名前
Thank you for taking care of Hisashi.
今日はありがとね 久志のこと
No problem.
(菜緒)いえ
You're his girlfriend, right?
彼女ってことで いいんだよね?
What? Whose girlfriend?
え?誰が誰の?
Hisashi's. You're Hisashi's girlfriend.
菜緒ちゃんが久志の
No, no! Not at all. We're just classmates.
いや全然違います ただの同級生です
What? Really?
え?そうなの?
That's unusual.
意外
There's not many people he's that relaxed with
久志が気を許す人って そうそういないからてっきり
I wouldn't call it relaxed. More like insulting.
気を許してるというか なめられてるというか
Oh! I have an idea!
あつそうだ!
Nao, can you also tell him
ねえ菜緒ちゃんからも 言ってくれない?
to come back home?
実家に帰ってこいって
Huh?
(菜緒)え?
He doesn't listen to a word I say.
あいつ私の言うこと 全く聞かないからさ
He's a real smart-ass, that man-brat.
本当生意気 フケガキのくせに
Man-brat?
フケガキ?
That's my nickname for Hisashi.
私が久志に付けたあだ名
He looks older than he is, but inside he's still a brat.
見た目は老けてんのに 中身はガキのまんま
So I call him man-brat.
だからフケガキ
I see. He sure is.
なるほど 確かに
Uh-oh. I've got to get back to the office.
ヤツバ 会社戻んなきゃ
What? Now?
え?今からですか?
Uh-huh. I'm an editor at an information magazine.
佰合) うん 情報誌の編集やってるんだけどさ
It's always like this before a deadline.
締め切り前は いつもこうなんだよね
It's a real pain. Bye.
やんなる じゃあ先行くね
Yuri sure was cool.
かっこよかったなあ つにな 百合さん
She's beautiful as well.
しかも美人
I wonder if I'll be like that in a few years too?
何年後かには ああいうふうになれるのかな
The hell you will.
(上原の声)なれるわけねーし
Huh?
え?
Is he...
あれ?
Damn him! I got so used to hearing his insults.
もう誰かさんのせいで うるさいのに慣れちゃったじゃん
You're such a jerk, Uehara!
上原君のバーカ!
Wait a minute...
っていうか
He's coming back, isn't he?
上原君 本当に帰ってくるんだよね
He's not going back to his home, right?
実家帰るなんて 言わないよね?
See ya!
じゃあな
Huh? W... wait! Wait!
ん?ちょっ... ちょっちよっちょっと!
This month's $1,500, please.
(ルミ子)今月分の15万円
Ah!
(菜緒)あ!
No! No way! I can't pay!
無理無理! それは無理!
What'll I do?
どうしよう
I'll keep Uehara here by winning him over with food.
上原君を捕まえるには 胃袋からだよね~
The amount of food is more important than the taste.
味より量で勝負でしょ
I'll make him tons of dishes.
片っ端から作って…
Oh, that scared me.
(菜緒)びっくりした
Yum!
ん~ !
They're really dating? What a shock!
(敦子)本当に付き合ってんの? 超ショックなんだけど
Totally! How could Uehara choose Yoshikawa?
(桜)ねつ っていうか 何で上原君が吉川菜緒?
Can you believe it?
(敦子)確かに 何で?
Yo! Morning, Daichi.
(男子生徒) おっ大地おはよう
-Morning.
(大地)おはよう (男子生徒)おはよう
Hiro, did you prep for Algebra II?
(まりかねえ広ちゃん 数11の予習やった?
Yeah, I did.
(広ちゃん) うんやったよ
Uh, there's a part I wanted to ask about.
(まりな)えーとねちょっと 教えてほしいところがあるんだよね
Where?
(広ちゃん)どこ?
We've got Music next. Let's go together.
次音楽だよね 一緒に行こ
Huh?
あれ?
Hey, Marina.
ねえまりな
What?
え
-Nao. -Yes?
(大地)菜緒 (菜緒)どうしたの?
Uh, nothing... I just...
ああいや…ちょっと
-Nao, are you-- -Marina's getting away.
菜緒ってさ… ご... (菜緒) まりな行っちゃう な仃つ
Sorry. We can talk later.
ごめん後でね
-Eek!
(菜緒。まりな) うわっ! な) つわつ
Darn you!
(菜緒)もう!
Quit following me.
しつこいよ
How come you're ignoring me?
(菜緒)何で無視すんの?
Because you lied to me.
ウソついたでしよ
You really are Uehara's girlfriend.
本当は上原君と 付き合ってるんだってね こつ
She is my girlfriend.
こいつ俺と付き合ってるから
How did you find out?
何で知ってんの?
Uehara of the top three has a girlfriend.
御三家の上原君が 彼女つくったんだよ
That kind of news spreads like wildfire.
そんなのあっという間に 広まるに決まってんじゃん
-But, you see-- -Don't get me wrong.
そのことなんだけど (まりな)勘違いしないでね
I'm not angry that you're Uehara's girlfriend.
私上原君と菜緒が付き合ってることで 女又 怒ってんじゃないから
What?
(菜緒)え...
I'm pissed at you
上原君とは何もないって ウソつかれたことに腹立ってんの!
I know it's not easy to tell me
そりゃ私散々 "上原君上原君,騒いでるから
But you and I have known each other for so much longer.
でも菜緒との付き合いのほうが ずっとずっと長いし
And I thought I was your best friend.
私は一番の友達だと 思ってたし!
It's like you're putting up a front,
こんなの表面だけ繕って
but in your heart, you're blowing me off.
心の中で シカトされてるようなもんじゃん
Marina...
まりな…
How come you're going to cry?
何で菜緒が 泣きそうになってんの
I'm sorry.
ごめん
Tell me everything from now on, OK? I'll tell you everything about me too.
次からはちゃんと話してよ 私も全部話すからさ
-OK. -Good.
(菜緒) うん... (まりな)よし
-I... -Yes?
(菜緒)私ね (まりな)ん?
To tell the truth, we're pretending to be dating.
実は上原君と 付き合ってるフリしてんの
What?
は?
Oh. Class is going to start.
あ…始まる
Huh? Hey!
(まりな)あ…え?
Hey, Wait! You'd better fill me in later! Wait!
あっちよっとちょっと! その話後でちゃんと聞かせて
You mean you and Uehara are living there together?
菜緒はあそこに上原君と 緒に住んでるってこと?
Hey! Who told you?
(菜緒)ちょっ...もう!
That's right. So to keep people from finding out
(まりな)そう で同居がバレないように
that they're living together, he said to pretend that they're dating.
付き合ってるフリしろって 言われたんだって
I thought he was a Prince Charming, but she says he's a stuck-up jerk.
白馬の王子様かと思いきや 超傲慢な王様だったわけよ
Yeah, that's absolutely right!
(菜緒)そうそうなんだよ!
What's worse, he's got everyone fooled.
しかもみんな 完全にだまされてんだよ
Isn't he awful, Mitsuishi?
ひどいと思わない? みつちゃん
Uh, but don't you think
(光石)いやそんなのより
the bigger problem is the fact you're living with a guy?
男と同居生活のほうが よっぽど問題のような
There haven't been any problems yet.
(菜緒)今んとこ問題ないよ
What're you talking about?
(光石)いやいや
Of course there has.
なくはないだろ
Are you taking that to Uehara at the hospital?
まりな)それ上原君の病院に 持って行くやつ?
Yep.
(菜緒) うん
It's part of my plan to use food to keep him from leaving.
家出て行かないように 食べ物で釣る作戦
So you were up all night cooking.
(まりな)で夜中まで C 起きて作ってたと
How did you know?
(菜緒)え!何で?
Rings under your eyes.
(まりな)クマ (菜緒)ハッ!
He's such a big eater, I thought I'd better make a lot.
上原君大食いだから いっぱい作んないとと思って
It took forever.
そしたら時間かかっちゃつて
You know, Nao, I think you like Uehara.
菜緒さやっぱ 上原君のこと好きでしょ?
What? Of course I don't!
(菜緒)はあ!?そんなことない
I never said anything like that.
私一言も そんなこと言ってないし
That's what's called
こういうのを 愛の成せる技っていうんだよ
I told you I'm not!
( 菜緒)だから違うってば!
Uehara has a real girlfriend.
上原君はちゃんと 彼女がいるんです!
-What? -What? Who?
(光石)はあ!? (まりな)え!誰誰?
His older brother's wife.
お兄さんの奥さん
She's super pretty. So cheerful and kind too.
すっごいきれいでね 明るくていい人で
Competent at her job as well.
仕事もできて
A real grown-up woman.
大人な女性って 感じなんだよね
I'm not visiting him.
やめたお見舞い
Why not?
え?
Because she can take care of him.
だってこの人が 面倒見てくれるんだもん
Yep. She'll do it.
うんそうだよ
She'll take care of him, so I'm not.
この人が見てくれるから やめた
I'm going to eat this myself.
私これ 自分で食べるからさ!
I'm not going. Nope. Not going.
やめたわやめた やめた!
Everyone I know is so blind to love.
本当私の周りって 色恋に鈍感なのばっかり
You are too.
お前もな
Did you say something?
何か言った?
No.
いや別に
Maybe I'll just look in on him.
様子だけでも見てきてやるか
God damn him!
もう何なの
Yo.
おお
What's that supposed to mean?
“おお,,じゃないよ!
You could at least tell me you were released.
退院するなら するって言ってよね!
I don't have your number.
俺お前の携帯知らねーし
Oh...
あ… め
Here.
はい
Don't always be contacting me. I hate Line and texting.
あんま連絡してくんなよ 俺LINEとかメールとか嫌いだから
Why would I contact you if I didn't have a reason?
用がなかったら 連絡なんてしません
What's that?
(上原)何それ
Oh... That's your dinner.
(菜緒)ああ 上原君用のお弁当
I'll have it for a midnight snack.
(上原)夜食にする
You should have dinner before that.
夜食ってまず夕食じゃ
Don't tell me that...
まさか
You ate it all!
食べられた
Hey!
ちよつと! ちょっと!
You broke the rules! You ate my food without permission!
ルール違反でしょ 人のもの勝手に食べて!
Oh...
(上原)ああゴホッゴホッ…
I'm recovering so I made an exception.
俺病み上がりだから 特別ルール適用した
What?
はあ!?
That ticks me off! Who said he could make an exception?
あったまくる~! 何よ特別ルールって
And how can he eat that much when he's supposed to be recovering?
っていうか病み上がりのくせに どんだけ食べんのよ!
He actually did come back here.
ちゃんと帰ってきたんだ 上原君.
Darn it all. And I was enjoying living alone so much.
あ~あ 人暮らし満喫してたのにな~ !
Oh, that's right.
あつそうだ
It's Mom.
(菜緒)お母さん
Are you eating nutritiously?
(美紀子) ちゃんと 栄養あるもの食べてるの?
You wouldn't believe it, but I'm cooking for myself.
(菜緒)そこはバッチリ ちゃんと自炊もしてるしね
Well, that's good to hear.
(美紀子)ならいいけど
Oh. You're not forgetting what your real job as a student is, right?
あっ学生の本分も 忘れてないでしようね?
I've got that covered too.
(菜緒)大丈夫大丈夫
It's so much easier to study when I'm living alone.
人暮らしのほうが 勉強もはかどるんだよね
Oh, is that so? Are you ready for your next final--
(美紀子)あらそう? じゃあ今度の期末テストも…
Trust me, Mom. I've changed.
(菜緒)任せてお母さん 私生まれ変わったから
I might even make it into the top half of the class.
学年で半分以内に 入れちゃうかも!
Really? That's great.
(美紀子)ならよかった
Your father and I talked this over.
お父さんとも 話してたんだけどね
If you're not in the top half, then you won't be living alone anymore.
半分以内に入らなかったら 一人暮らし終了ね
OK. Piece of cake.
うん楽勝楽勝!
Really? I'm looking forward to it.
(美紀子)そう? じゃあ楽しみにしてるわ
OK. Bye.
は~いじゃあね!
Did I really say, piece of cake?
楽勝って言っちゃつた…
When are finals?
期末テストって いつだつけ?
From Tuesday.
火曜から…今日は土曜
Saturday, Sunday, Monday.
土日月
Oh, no!
ハッ! ハツ
I'm more likely to be out of here than Uehara is.
上原君より私のほうが 出て行く可能性高いかも
I've got to study!
勉強しなくちゃ
Welcome home. Must be hard working so early.
早朝からバイト ご苦労さまです
Yeah, thanks.
(上原)おお
Were you up all night?
お前寝てないの?
Tests are coming up.
(菜緒)テストあるからね
Oh, yeah. Must be tough being stupid.
(上原)ああアホは大変だな
Are you OK?
大丈夫?お前
Oh, yeah!
そうだ
I've got you!
上原君がいる
Uehara! Tutor me, please!
上原君 勉強教えてお願い!
-No. -What?
(上原)やだ (菜緒)えっ
-Why not? -It'd be a real pain.
何でよ (上原)面倒くさい
And you seem like a poor learner. All it would do is exhaust me.
しかもお前物覚え悪そうだし 俺すっげー疲れそうだし
All you do is complain.
ちょっと言いたい放題
You really are a man-brat.
自分なんか フケガキのくせに
Did you and Yuri...
お前百合と.
Forget it.
何でもない
Oh, no! I haven't made any progress!
ヤバい 全然進んでない
I can't understand...
分かんない
Sorry, I can't.
(大地)悪い
We've got a practice game today.
俺今日 部活の練習試合あってさ
Oh, I see. Yeah, I guess you're busy.
そっかだよね 忙しいのにごめんね
You've always been the type
お前本当追い詰められないと 全然やらないタイプだもんな
Summer vacation homework, research projects and book reports.
夏休みの宿題自由研究 読書感想文
Oh, yeah. Your somersault practice too.
あああと逆上がりの 練習もあったな
You helped me with all those, Daichi.
全部大ちゃんに 手伝ってもらいました…
It'd be nice if you appreciated me a little more.
俺もうちょい感謝されても いいと思うんだけどな~
I do, Daichi.
してるよ大ちゃん
I totally appreciate what you've done.
私大ちゃんに すっごい感謝してます!
OK, I'll do it.
じゃあよし!
But I really do need to stop depending on you.
本当私大ちゃんから 早く卒業しなきゃだよね
Yes?
ん?
Nothing. Do your best. Bye.
いや…頑張れよ じゃあな
OK. Thanks. Bye.
うんありがと じゃあね
That's Yuri.
百合?
That was close.
危ねえ
OA times OB cosine C
(菜緒) OAかけるOB コサイン
minus one half, parentheses, A times B...
マイナス2分の1 カッコAかけるB 1B
Huh? What was it again?
ありゃ?何だっけ
Oh! It's vector.
あ…ベクトルだ
-Huh? -Hey there.
(菜緒)ん? 佰刽やっほ~ んや )ノ)ノ
Yuri!
百合さん!
-Yum! It's delicious! -This is great.
(百合) うんおいしい (菜緒) う~ん
It's delicious.
(菜緒)おいしい
I'm so glad I ran into you, Nao.
佰刽でもよかった 菜緒ちゃんに会えて
I left him a message to say I was going to drop by
あいつの家に行くって 留守電入れたのに 寸电
Could you call him for me, Nao?
菜緒ちゃんからも 電話してくれない?
I can't get in unless he's there.
あいついなきゃ 部屋入れないもん
Oh, I think he's working today. Probably...
あ~今日はバイトかな? な
What? He is?
えっそうなの?
Darn him. Why can't he just call? He's such a pain.
もう連絡よこせっつーの 本当かわいくない奴
Uhm, Yuri...
あの百合さん
Why don't you call me Yuririn?
私のことは "ゆりりんって呼んで
Yuririn?
ゆりりん?
Right. And you don't have to talk so polite.
そう あと敬語もいらないからね
Then, Yuririn...
じゃあゆりりん
Yes? What is it?
佰合) うん?なーに?
Uhm...
あの…
Uehara... Is he...
上原君は あの…その
Did he say something about me?
佰合)何か言ってた?あいつ
But... when he's with you, he seems different than usual.
でも…ゆりりんといる時は いつもと違うっていうか
He looks so pained.
つらそうな顔するから
I think I was his first love.
あいつの初恋の相手 私みたい
Really?
え?
Takuya and Hisashi's family and mine were friends,
(百合)旦那の卓也と久志とは 家族ぐるみで仲良くてさあ
The three of us would always play around as kids.
ちっちゃい頃から 3人でドタバタやってたわけ
But when their parents died, they became depressed.
でもご両親が亡くなって 2人とも元気なくしちゃつて…
I said I'd be their mother instead.
私自分が 母親代わりになるって
So I was always over at their house.
ますます上原家に 出入りするようになって
Then I fell in love with him... Takuya, I mean.
好きになっちゃつたのよね 卓也のこと
Hisashi is like a little brother to me.
久志は弟みたいなもんでさ
I had absolutely no clue that he had a crush on me.
私なんかに恋心抱いてるなんて 全然気づかなくて
Not long after, we got married
私が結婚して上原家に住み始めて 少し経った頃かな
He told me.
言われちゃつたのよね
"I can't live with the woman I like and her husband."
“好きな女とその旦那とは 一緒に暮らせないって
It must have been hard for him. I really felt bad about it.
(百合)つらかったと思うよ 申し訳ないって思ってる
But...
でもさ..
But, seriously!
でもだよ?
Takuya and I were newlyweds and so in love.
私と卓也新婚だしラブラブだし しょうがなくない?
If he liked me, then he should have said sooner!
好きなら好きって 最初から言えっつーの!
Well, I guess that
まあ確かに
getting drunk and kissing him a bunch probably gave him the wrong idea.
酔っ払って何回もキスしたのは 勘違いさせたかもだけど
What?
ええつ!?
Oh, dear. I'll kiss anyone when I'm drunk.
ああ私酔っ払うと 誰にでもキスしちやうんだよね
Oh, really.
(菜緒)そうなんだ
I'm sure I've kissed Hisashi 20 times.
久志には20回はしてるね
What? 20 times?
え!20回?
Are you jealous?
ヤキモチやいちやった?
No. There's nothing between us--
別に私と上原君は 何でもないです。
Yeah, yeah. Sure. OK!
佰刽はいはいよし!
Since I've come all this way, I may as well see his place.
せっかくここまで来たし 久志の家だけでも見て帰るか
Huh? What? Wait! Wait!
(菜緒)えっえ…え ちょっちょっと...
Wait!
ちよつと! ちょっと!
You forgot this!
忘れてるって!
Hold on!
ちょっと待って あつ!
Yes. I'm OK.
(上原)はい まあ
Seriously, I'm just fine.
全然大丈夫ですって
It's alright. Don't push yourself when you're still ill.
(明)いいんだいいんだ 体調悪いのに無理しなくて
I'm good. I really am all better.
(上原)いやもう本当に 完全に治って
Take the day off and relax.
(明)今日は1日 ゆっくり休みなさい
Bye.
じゃあね
Uehara...
(ななこ)久志君
He hung up?
切れてた?
If they're going to cancel, I wish they'd tell us sooner.
(雄平)中止なら中止で もっと早く連絡よこせよな
They said they caught the flu.
(駿介)相手インフルだってよ
What? Seriously?
(雄平)ゲッマジで
See you.
(大地)お疲れ
-See you later. -See you.
(駿介)お疲れさまです (雄平)お疲れっす
Hey!
休地よっ!
Oh, Daichi. Where are you headed?
(まりな)ああ大ちゃん どこ行くの?
Nao's place.
(大地)菜緖んち
Our game was cancelled, so I'm going over to tutor her.
部活の試合中止になったから 勉強教えてやろうと思ってさ
Later.
じゃあな
Nao's place?
菜緖んち?
Uh... There'll be trouble if Uehara's there.
(光石)え. 上原君したらマズいよな?
Serious trouble. Daichi's kind of old-fashioned.
相当ヤバいよ 大ちゃんお堅いタイプだもん
If he found out that Nao and Uehara are living together...
がったら... 菜緒と上原君が 同居してるって知ったら… つに
What would happen?
どうなんの?
Run, Mitsuishi!
走るよみつちゃん!
Oh, my god!
ヤバいヤバい...
Seriously?
マジで?
Let's jump rope.
(子供たち)縄跳びやろうぜ
Come on, Mitsuishi. Hurry up!
(まりな) ちょっ…みつちゃん 早く!
Yes?
佰刽ん?
Yo!
(大地85 (大地)おう
-Uh...
(EDR) A...
Who are you?
誰?
Isn't this Yoshikawa Nao's place?
ここって 吉川菜緒の家だよね
God damn her.
あの野郎…
Aren't you the junior, Uehara?
2年の上原君?
Yeah. What of it?
そっすけど
What are you doing in Nao's place?
何で菜緒の家にいんの?
Hello there! We're coming in, Uehara.
どうも~! 上原君お邪魔しま~す
What're you two doing?
(上原)何なんだよお前ら
Leave this to us.
いいからここは 私たちに任せて
Huh? Hey!
(上原)は?おい!
Hey! I'm not finished talking to you!
(大地)おいちょっとまだ 話終わってねえぞ
Daichi, don't get so worked up, OK?
(光石)大地先輩 そんな殺気立たずにね?
Hey, guys!
ねえ!
I've got milk tea. Why don't we take a break?
ミルクティーがあるよ とりあえずブレイクする?
-Hey! That's mine! -What?
(上原)お前それ俺の! (まりな)え?ちょっとえ…
-Give it back. Give it back. -Wait! Stop!
(上原)返せ 返せよ
Uehara! Are you and Nao--
(大地)上原! お前と菜緒と…
I'm drinking this!
いただきま~す
That's mine. Don't you dare!
(上原)だから 人の勝手に飲むんじゃねー
Who cares about that--
休地) そんなもんどうでもいいから.
Now, now. Take a deep breath.
(光石) 1回深呼吸しましょう 深呼吸
Get out of my way, Mitsuishi!
(大地)光石邪魔だ!
Oh! Look at all these people!
みんなで集まってんの?
What fun!
楽しそ~!
-Nice to meet all of you. -Nao!
初めまして (大地)菜緒
I'm Hisashi's sister-in-law, Yuri.
久志の義理の姉の 百合で~す
Nao...
EJll...
-God damn you! -Are you all Hisashi's friends?
(上原)お前… (百合)み~んな久志のお友達?
Of course they're not!
全員ちげーよ!
Really?
佰合)え?
Nao, are you Uehara's girlfriend?
(大地)菜緒お前 上原と付き合ってんのか?
Uh...
あ… め
Daichi! Daichi!
(まりな)大ちゃん大ちゃん...
Nao's living with him, but she's not his girl--
菜緒は一緒に住んでるけど 付き合ってはいない…
What? Living together?
(大地)はあ!? 一緒に住んでる
You're living with Hisashi?
(百合)菜緒ちゃん 久志と同棲してんの?
I knew it! You're his girlfriend.
やっぱ彼女なんだ-?
No, I'm not!
(菜緒)違う違う違う!
We are living together--
同居は違くなくて
Pretend! They're pretending dating!
(光石)フリ! 付き合ってるフリしててな!
That's right!
(菜緒)そう!
Why do you have to live together if you're just pretending?
(大地)何でフリで 一緒に住む必要があるんだよ
Wait a minute!
佰刽まさか!
Are you after her body, Hisashi?
久志菜緒ちゃんの 体目当てじゃ
After her body?
体目当てって
-No way! How shameful! -It's total chaos!
まりな)ウソ!結構大胆 壮 (光石)カオスだ!
What the hell are you thinking--
佰合)ちょっとあんた 一体何考えて.
Shut up!
うるせーつ!
I'll tell you everything.
全部話すから
So everybody, just shut up.
とりあえず全員黙れ
Ow!
(光石)イテテテ
That's the story. All of it.
(上原) というわけ 以上
Yay!
(まりな)んん~!
I've got no interest in her at all.
いや俺は こいつのこと何とも思ってないし
Damn, you're awfully frank.
そ…そんな ハッキリ言わなくても
She feels the same about me. We're simply living together.
それはこいつも同じ 本当純粋な同居人
Right?
なつ?
Yes... That's exactly right.
はい...そのとおりです
Besides, she's moving to the dorms in April.
しかもこいつは 4月から寮に移るし
And I plan to save enough money to move by then.
俺もそれまでに金ためて 引っ越すつもりだから
So I'd like to continue... living together like this.
できるならこのまま 同居を続けたいと思ってる
Uhm...
あの…
This is the first time... Uehara and I have lived alone.
私と上原君は お互い初めて一人暮らしして
We're trying to figure things out, so we're alike in that.
ドタバタした 同志みたいなもんで
I'm not like you.
緒にすんなよ
We always fight,
ケンカもしょっちゅうするけど
but since we're alike, we understand each other.
でも同志だから 分かり合えるし
It's reassuring.
心強いっていうか
So, I know you're worried about us,
(菜緒)なので ご心配もおありかと思いますが
but...
同居続けさせてください! お願いします
Yuri.
(菜緒)百合さん
I'm sorry I kept it secret that we were living together.
同居のこと秘密にしてて ごめんなさい
It doesn't bother me at all.
(百合)全然気にしてないよ
I understand what Hisashi's situation is.
久志の状況も分かったし
Since it's with you, Nao, I feel good about it.
相手が菜緒ちゃんなら 私も一安心
Yuri.
百合さん
OK, see you later. Take care of Hisashi.
じゃあまたね 久志のことよろしく
-Nao. -Yes?
菜緒 (菜緒)ん?
I thought Uehara and Yuri were having an affair.
百合さんて 上原君と不倫じゃなかったの?
-I misunderstood. -How could you do that?
(菜緒)勘違いだった (光石)何だよそれ だそ いよ
Well, I was half right.
半分はだけど
Huh?
(光石·まりな)ん?
What?
(上原)何すか?
I can't understand your way of thinking at all.
お前の考えてること 全然分かんないわ
Huh?
仩原)は?
How can you live with a total stranger? And she's a girl too?
普通住むか? 見ず知らずの奴とそれも女と
-What business is it of yours? -Are you doing this because it's Nao?
あんたに関係あるんでしたっけ? (大地)菜緒だからか?
Because you think she'll be easy to control?
扱いやすそうとでも思った?
And so what if I do?
だったらどうなんすか?
You're the type
お前ってさ
that hurts others without even knowing it.
無意識のうちに 人のこと傷つけるタイプだろ
What does that mean?
どういう意味?
Exactly like it sounds.
そのまんまの意味だよ
Oh!
(菜緒)あ...
Daichi... You're angry, aren't you?
大ちゃん… 女又 怒ってるよね?
I'm really sorry I didn't tell you.
黙ってて本当ごめん
If anything happens, you come straight over to my place.
(大地何かあったら すぐに俺んち来いよ
OK.
(菜緒) うん
Thanks for everything.
お疲れさまでした
Christ! You've been nothing but trouble for me.
仩原) ったく お前といるとろくなことないな
How dare you! Quit acting like it's all my fault.
何よ 全部私が悪いみたいに
You brought them all over here, right?
あいつら連れてきたの お前だろうが
Yes. I'm sorry.
はいすいません
Well, at least it all worked out.
まあ何とか うまくいってよかったわ
Huh? What?
え?何?
High five.
ハイタッチ
Ow! Why do you have to use such force?
(上原)イッテ!お前何で そんな馬鹿力なんだよ
Anyway, we can breathe a little easier now.
とりあえず一安心だね
You really are happy-go-lucky. I'm going to bed.
お前本当お気楽だよな 俺もう寝る
Oh, no!
ああー!
What's wrong?
どうした
-Tests... -Huh?
テスト… 仩原)は?
If I don't get a good score on my tests, I'll have to go back home.
私テストでいい点数取んないと 実家行き!
Are you kidding me?
何それ
I told you before! How come you can't understand this?
だから! 何でこんなのも分かんねんだよ
I can't help it if I can't understand. It's not my fault.
分かんないものは分かんないんだから しようがないでしょ
Use the formula, damn it.
公式を使え公式を!
I told you too!
(菜緒)だから!
There are so many formulas. There's one here too.
公式いっぱいあんの こっちにも
It's this one.
これなんだって
-Which one? -Not that one.
(菜緒)どれ? (上原)そっち関係ない
It's so hard!
(菜緒)ややこしいの!
What? It's your head that's hard.
(上原)は? ややこしいのはお前の頭だよ
-Cut it out! That hurt. -How come you can't...
(菜緒)やめてよ痛いな (上原)だから何で
-Chiho Yoshida. -Yes.
(教師)吉田ちほさん (吉田)はい
-Atsushi Yonekawa.
(教師)米川あつしさん (米川)はい
One above the half-way line.
(菜緒)半分より1つ上
I did it! I'm in!
入った やった つに
I did it!
やったー!
I did it, Uehara! 87th place!
(菜緒) "やったよ上原君! つに 87番! ,,
I won't have to go back to the countryside!
“田舎に連れ戻されなくて すみました!"
Just barely. That sure was close.
ギリじゃねーかよ 危ねーな
To thank you, I'll treat you something nice. You want milk pudding?
(菜緒) “お礼に何かおごるよ 牛乳プリンでいい?"
Yeah.
おお
Got it.
了解!
Yes! I'm in luck.
(上原)おっラッキ
Huh? What?
(菜緒)え?え?
Hey! Wait! What? You're getting them all?
え...ちょっ...え? 全部買うの?
-Come on. -What?
(上原)おい
-They've got big size too. -What?
(上原)ロングあるじゃん (菜緒)え?
Ah!
(菜緒)あっ!
Oh! That's good too.
あつあれうまいんだよなあ
-Start with rock! -Rock!
(上原)最初はグー! (菜緒)グー! 初!
-Rock-paper-scissors!
(上原,菜緒) ゃんけんポイ! じ
-It's a tie!
あいこでしょ!
-Ah... -Yes!
(菜緒)あ... 仩原)シャー!
Come on.
(上原)ほれ
Me again?
(菜緒) また私?
Oh, alright.
(上原) しゃーねーな
-Thank-- -Here.
(菜緒)あり 仩原)ほれ
Here.
ほれ
"Here! Here!" What a jerk!
何なの? “ほれほれ,,
Damn it!
もう!
So heavy... They're so heavy.
重いな~ 重…重いな~
Could you please carry just one? Just one.
1つぐらい 1つ持ってほしいな~
Please carry just one.
1つ持ってほしい
Oh, alright.
(上原) しゃーねーな
I'll carry these potato sticks.
フレンチポテトだけ 持ってやるよ
What?
(菜緒)え!
Hey!
ちよつと! ちょっと!
Here you go.
(菜緒)はーいお待たせ
-OK. Let's eat. -Let's eat.
(上原)よし いただきます (菜緒)いただきます した よい
Don't copy me.
マネすんなよ
You too.
そっちこそ っていうか
You've got to start with the plain first.
最初はベーシックで 攻めるもんだろ
What? That doesn't make any sense at all.
は? 全然意味分かんない
-First come, first served. -Ah! Hey!
(上原)早いもん勝ち~! (菜緒)あっ!ちょっ
What?
何よ
You can have half.
半分やる
I bought it for myself in the first place.
もともと私が買ったやつだし
It's Yuri.
(菜緒)百合さんだ
You're not going to answer?
出ないの?
I've got nothing to talk about.
何も用ねーし
Even if you don't, Yuri might--
(菜緒)上原君はなくても 百合さんのほうが
Shut up.
うっせえ
Yum.
(上 ) う~ん 原
You're just like an elementary school boy.
何か小学生の男の子みたい
What?
仩原)はあ?
The kind that teases the girl he likes.
好きな子には 意地悪するってやつ?
Sorry.
ごめん
What're you apologizing for?
(上原)何で謝んだよ
You're right? Why am I?
だよね そうだよね
Uehara,
上原君ってさ
you like Yuri, don't you?
やっぱ百合さんのこと 好きなんだよね?
Sorry. Go ahead and eat all of them.
ごめんこれ全部食べて
I've got to tell Mom about my tests.
私お母さんに テストの報告しなきゃ
Good night.
おやすみ
It's so clear...
to...
Uehara... has always liked Yuri.
上原君は ずっと百合さんのことが好き.
What the...
あれ…
Why am I...
何で…
That day was the first time
(菜綯その日初めて私は
I realized that I might be in love with Uehara.
上原君が好きなのかもしれない と思った...